import { Exercise } from ".";

export const COUNTRIES: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "Россия",
    "answer": "Rossija",
    "extra": "🇷🇺"
  },
  {
    "question": "Польша",
    "answer": "Polsza",
    "extra": "🇵🇱"
  },
  {
    "question": "Испания",
    "answer": "Ispanija",
    "extra": "🇪🇸"
  },
  {
    "question": "Франция",
    "answer": "Francija",
    "extra": "🇫🇷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Германия",
    "answer": "Giermanija",
    "extra": "🇩🇪"
  },
  {
    "question": "Италия",
    "answer": "Italija",
    "extra": "🇮🇹"
  },
  {
    "question": "США",
    "answer": "SZA (Sojediniennyje Sztaty Amieriki)",
    "extra": "🇺🇸"
  },
  {
    "question": "Канада",
    "answer": "Kanada",
    "extra": "🇨🇦"
  },
  {
    "question": "Бразилия",
    "answer": "Brazylija",
    "extra": "🇧🇷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Австралия",
    "answer": "Australija",
    "extra": "🇦🇺"
  },
  {
    "question": "Великобритания",
    "answer": "Wielikobritanija",
    "extra": "🇬🇧"
  },
  {
    "question": "Япония",
    "answer": "Japonija",
    "extra": "🇯🇵"
  },
  {
    "question": "Китай",
    "answer": "Kitaj",
    "extra": "🇨🇳"
  },
  {
    "question": "Индия",
    "answer": "Indija",
    "extra": "🇮🇳"
  },
  {
    "question": "Мексика",
    "answer": "Mieksika",
    "extra": "🇲🇽"
  },
  {
    "question": "Аргентина",
    "answer": "Argientina",
    "extra": "🇦🇷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Египет",
    "answer": "Jiegipt",
    "extra": "🇪🇬"
  },
  {
    "question": "Южная Африка",
    "answer": "Juznaja Afrika",
    "extra": "🇿🇦"
  },
  {
    "question": "Турция",
    "answer": "Turcija",
    "extra": "🇹🇷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Греция",
    "answer": "Grecija",
    "extra": "🇬🇷"
  },
  {
    "question": "Швеция",
    "answer": "Szwecja",
    "extra": "🇸🇪"
  },
  {
    "question": "Норвегия",
    "answer": "Norwegija",
    "extra": "🇳🇴"
  },
  {
    "question": "Финляндия",
    "answer": "Finlandija",
    "extra": "🇫🇮"
  },
  {
    "question": "Дания",
    "answer": "Danija",
    "extra": "🇩🇰"
  },
  {
    "question": "Нидерланды",
    "answer": "Nidierłandy",
    "extra": "🇳🇱"
  },
  {
    "question": "Швейцария",
    "answer": "Szwejcarija",
    "extra": "🇨🇭"
  },
  {
    "question": "Австрия",
    "answer": "Austrija",
    "extra": "🇦🇹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ирландия",
    "answer": "Irlandija",
    "extra": "🇮🇪"
  },
  {
    "question": "Португалия",
    "answer": "Portugałija",
    "extra": "🇵🇹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Южная Корея",
    "answer": "Juznaja Korieja",
    "extra": "🇰🇷"
  }
];
